all right 3 challenge black dust cloud
arm Arsenal EG Academy and flashbang
Revenge so we've got a s blade we've got
an M M20 and we've got a lot of Aegis
units or in this case juggernauts but
aside from that we've also got flashbang
Revenge
which literally does not mean anything
at all it is not a threat now we'll
shoot
those right then thanks now we're going
to get right over to the defend we help
of the juggernauts because the
juggernauts are kind of the main threat
here but then again there's one good
thing about the saw blade we can get
free ammunition from the
Juggernaut and it has a lot of
bullets so in other words we have a
weapon that can for all intents and
purposes fire infinitely I
mean we can't actually do that but that
might as well be the case I mean there
there is
literally no reason to fire continuously
indefinitely
but what we're doing right
now it's entirely
self-sustainable just because of the
juggernauts anyways that door should be
open soon so we're going to help out a
bit more with getting those shotgunners
because they will for absolutely no
reason at all Rush us we'll go through
via here and then afterwards we'll go
all the way here to the
door
cyber you have the breaching
charge right then we El un this breach
over there which we're not going to
worry too much about we'll check for a
screwdriver which is not present and now
we're just going to watch out for any
units that show
up that's all of them
clear I mean
it's free
ammunition but they're all
cbc's and while we could use cbrc we're
not going to do that right
anyways surely there are some
juggernauts I want that free ammunition
and Med kits but regardless we finished
blow torching so we're just going to go
right through here and then
afterwards s's going to breach into
there what I'm going to do is I'm not
actually going to plant anything there
because I don't need to I'm going to go
over here and I'm
actually after a bit of scuff
reorganizing going to grab myself a
drill for no real reason
actually it's really just
so I have safety in
case I'll take this
spot right then St I recommend you back
off in that
situation I'll take those three medits
that's for sure can I
can I actually grab those Med
kits all right squad's not going to
spawn there which
is that is a very ambitious whe taking
care of things we're going to go up here
I'm pretty sure there are units down
there which were just shooting at
me but we're doing fine so I'm sure
it'll be
fine all right no absolutely you are not
rushing me absolutely no you're not
doing that all right half all of that
clear and
then why is there more there's going to
be more now watch
no that's
predicted well then I mean cyber why are
you still here move just
move it's not that
complicated go over there and go
upstairs it's really not that
complicated and now all we're going to
do is defend for a
bit cyber you have way too many med kits
I mean I'll use one of them I don't
mind
and shotguns are the
worse right then in that case I assume
you're going to go with me now and
afterwards you
really take care of both juggernauts let
it breathe for a bit let those
flashbangs go grab that free ammunition
that I need that I actually need it
let's go this way let's just go down
over here just so that those juggernauts
won't cause us any it'll be fine let's
just go past all of that and those
juggernauts will definitely not cause us
any they just reach that door which I
mean sure go off the Cyber for like care
and now we'll go up here and we
will the Juggernaut are coming back over
here r& D you know what we'll grab that
we'll go over here and we'll use our
drill to get in get into
development and then afterwards we'll
breach that door and we'll plant a few
bombs it's really not that
complicated well you should
probably this is a very questionable
strategy right
then should I even try and get
that does it
even there isn't even a breaching charge
in that back and I am not intending to
go up and try and find out so we're just
going to use our drill over here and
we'll watch out for any units that show
up and we we will hopefully get through
this door in a decent amount of time
before any units show
up cyber having a great time over there
I'm certainly having a great time over
here too anyways we Bri the door we're
going to plant this bomb over here and
we'll plant this bomb over here and hi
there I see
you very
pesy
right they've still got the bombs on
them
I'm not
surprised I really can't say I am right
then you can drop the drill at least
that's for sure we can grab that extra
ammunition and now we
can you know my problem with this is the
fact that they're all cbc's but that's
besides the point we'll grab all of this
we will not grab those medits because we
don't need it but what we will do is
we'll grab those bombs and we'll try and
stay aware of whatever's going on over
here because we kind of need to so we'll
go upstairs and we'll plant the Bombs
over here while cyber figures out
whatever's going on over there which I
mean you should probably heal up right
now right around now it would be a
fantastic time to do
so we'll grab the med kit for no reason
in particular and you know what I mean
it's too late to go back over there
anyways but we could just steal with the
jugg off from over
here who else
prone because pring Thea blade is
actually pretty good for reducing recoil
and spread and we still got a 100
bullets to deal with
it
so I assume this is
actually all right that was almost much
more High there that was much much more
Awkward than it needed to be if I had to
use my mm20 but as the in just under 7
minutes and 40 seconds
people should use slbl more cheers
everyone have a great time
[Music]